Hello.
Where are you from?
Moscow.
Understood.  You have such fashionable glasses.
Did you buy this on Wris?
No, it's Tony.
Understood.  How do you communicate?
On various topics.
On various topics.  Don't know.
Pony.  Listen, since you're from the Moscow
region, from Moscow, it's true that
you had some flights there and the Wilbury warehouses burned down
,
right?
Why can't Russia protect them,
what do you think?  Everything,
that
everything is protected?
Why can't it protect its
civilian industry of all kinds?
Well, out of a thousand drones, if you hit,
say, 10, what percentage?
I don't know.
Well, do the math.  Are you
friends in mathematics?
Badly.
Bad, huh?  How much is this?  10 from a thousand.   It
will be 10% of 1100.  And how much will it be?  13%
of 13.
13% of 13, and
1.3 is not 1.69,
because 13 times 13 is 169.
Well, that’s why it
didn’t work out for you, right?
You're being overdone.
Well, you understand that there's no such thing as, like,
straight up, let's talk
about percentages now,
you understand that you wanted to get along with
percentages, yes, but you really didn't
succeed.  You screwed up.  But that's not what I
wanted to say.
Now go ahead and tell me how it was
n't possible for you.  I wanted to
state the protocol.   Can
you hear me?
I hear.  Tell me, come on, cry.
Well, I'm just saying that there is no
country that could provide
complete protection.
Of course, of course.   Yes.
Ukraine shoots down so many things.
Ukraine doesn't even have anything to shoot down with.
I'm surprised that Ukraine didn't
surrender in 2-3 days.
She was going to,
I don't know.  Well, damn,
how can you even stand up to Russia, a nuclear power
?
How can Iran present this?
So Iran, a nuclear power, is also
against it.  And look, there
is no ground operation against Iran.  Nobody is
sending troops to Tehran.
And there is the first army in the world.
Ah, but they were still standing here, that means these
troops were standing near Kiev.  By the way, can you
tell me where they went?
And there was a Turkish agreement.
What Turkish agreement?
Istanbul.
And what did it consist of?  And what do
you imagine is that there were such agreements
, that they were supposedly good, but now
they are much worse. And in what way?  Here, for example, is
what was agreed in these agreements
that Russia would withdraw its troops.
And, by the way, in Istanbul, yes, yes,
in Istanbul there were no Zaporizhzhia and
Kherson yet.
Once again, once again.  Well, look, I'm
just curious what they agreed on:
that Russia withdraws its troops, and
in exchange,
Ukraine, uh, reduces its army.  There are also
many points there.  There, Ukraine
is reducing its army, Ukraine is also
withdrawing troops.
So wait, did I understand correctly that
Russia began to withdraw its troops, but
Ukraine did not begin to withdraw?  Yes.
And you remember,
I'm just asking you.  So, Russia
ended up being the loser in this scheme?
Why?
Well, because it turns out that Russia is
now in worse conditions for you.
I don't know.  Now we are at 20. Now
the conditions are better, now they are worse.
The conditions are better now.  Now we are already
setting conditions, yes, in 20, but look, in
1922 we did not bomb
Russian territory, we did not leave it without
oil refineries.  Yes, it's
true.  And now somehow we already have
ballistics.
So it's better for you, right?
Yes, it's better for us, of course.  We are
already speaking from a position of strength.
Ah, from a position of strength.
Well, of course.   Wow
.
Look at this.  [clears throat] In the twenty-
second year.  In 22,
when Russian troops were stationed near Kiev
, yes, all the Russians said:
“My drones don’t fly, my missiles
don’t fly.”  Yes.  And now they’re already
crying, recording some videos about how
goods burned there, there’s no gasoline.
And in the twenty-second year, you
remember, in the twenty-second year there
was no TCC.  Remember these tricks?   There
wasn't any at all.  There was nothing at all.
Yes, I repeat.   Yes.
But look, we are interested in what is in
Russia.  Russians lived peacefully in
1922, but now
something bad has happened to them.  They are
worried now.
We are not whiners like you.  We're kind of
super, right?  Yes, we are more whiners, yes.
But I like it, for example, I don’t see, I do
n’t see after the Russians’ arrivals in
Ukraine, yes, how they cry.  Oh my God, my
goods, in short, at Nova Poshta, my goods at
Nova Poshta burned up.  Yes, we are
worried about the people who died.  And you,
yes, but what about the panties that burned on Vilber
, yes, these Insta-samochki
of all kinds, people are fighting, yes, you and I
helped each other, you fight in
lines for gas, scoreboards for each other.
Well, agree, let's still have the thesis in the
twenty-second today, look today
takite, you know, takitegi like they are
disposable takite.  Look,
we're comparing 1922 and 1926.
Ukraine did not attack Russian territory, but
now it does.
Wait, will you let me speak?  You
allow it, go ahead, I allow it.  Do you
allow me?   Yes.
Well, you asked me to give it.  I
give it to you.  I give permission.
No.  Why do I need permission?
Well, you asked me to let you
speak.  You asked, I give you permission.   Well, yes
.
You asked me to let you speak.
You're like, you're not like,
you don't look, if you want to say,
you take it yourself, right?  And you asked me to
give you the right to speak.  I give you the
right to say.  Speak.
Normal person.  Like I just
asked you: "And what about you, how inadequate are you?"
I gave you the right to speak.  Come on, tell me,
what are you crying about?  You're like an inadequate
person, you always say, like, I'm like,
guys, I'll pay, like, I'll give
you, in short,
I gave you the right to speak, go ahead and speak.
Look, you're already making excuses instead of
saying what you wanted to
say.  Come on, man,
look at it this way, the point is that in
1922, yes, you were standing near
Kiev and you bombed our territory, right?
Now in the twenty-sixth year we are bombing
your territory.  There are no troops near
our capital.  We are destroying your
industry, yes, damn, with missiles,
drones, yes.  We are making your
people suffer, your economy is going to
hell.  Yes, we have it better now than in
twenty-second, yes, because where do you get pi
?
In Krasnodar, in Podolsk, in Voronezh, in
Ryazan, in Saratov.
You understand that
this conflict will just get worse from here on out,
right?  It's getting worse at the moment,
right?  To worsen.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You know, wait, like, I'm giving you
this destruction for that shut up.  This is
dada.  And what will happen?
It's in this regard, you know?
To worsen.  And what about nuclear weapons?  This is
hazel.  Kukreshnik.
Well, of course, yes.  Well, wait,
when when nuclear
Are you waiting for this?
Yes, we are waiting.  We were already waiting at twenty-second
.  in twenty-third, twenty-
fourth.  Listen, you have some kind of
inadequacy,
look, well, fairy tales about nuclear weapons, you
understand, right, that you are talking about war, right?  You
are losing the war, so why talk about
nuclear weapons?  You don't have any trump cards anymore, that's it,
you don't have any cards, as Trump said,
where do you get them?
I'll tell you again, in Ryazan, in
Saratov, in Tula, in short, and so on.
How much territory have you recaptured since 1922
?
Super, I'll tell you.  We recaptured the Kyiv
region, we recaptured the Kharkov region.
So, they won it back
.  Again.  And one more thing.  Well, listen, come on, one more time
.  The Kyiv region was
captured, your troops were there and
recaptured it.  You yourself said that it is Yes.   The
Kharkiv region was captured.
Was.  They won it back.   They
fought back, yes.  Uh, autumn of '22
, yes.  Your escape from the
Kharkiv region, yes.  It was very
beautiful, wasn't it?  Our troops liberated the Kharkiv
region.  The city of Kherson moved out of Kherson.
I get it, I get it, I get it.  In short,
you haven't had any achievements for a year, have you?  Only 2 of these
achievements have you had since 4 years.
Why?  Look, right now, for example,
let's look at the past
month, if you look, yes, Ukraine
has recaptured more territory than Russia.
Look at the balance.  Look, yeah, come on,
come on, come on.  Where?  Look, yes.
Institute for the Study of War.
Come on, Deepstay, open up.
Okay, I'm telling you, go ahead and open it and
check.
Come on, what has Ukraine done in 20 years?
Here, take this and compare the balance of
territories lost and conquered by
Ukraine.  Let's have the
fifth one for two,
okay?  No, for last month, for this
June, like June.  June of the twenty-sixth
year.
Well, like, the beginning of twenty-six,
right?
June twenty-sixth year.  Here,
take this from last month.  We are fresh.  Let me
take it for six months.  Okay, let's take it.  We
are looking at the dynamics.  Let's take
last month.
No, let's not give it to you in a year, straight away, for 25.
And you're like bam.
Come on, take this, this last,
this last month.
What's there?  What kind of dynamics is this?
Why are you afraid to take last month?
I just didn't look.
Well, look, come on, come on tell me,
come on tell me your details, come on talk.
No.  And I asked you, like, Ukraine,
something like in six months, in a year.  It was me, I
told you, I told you.
My, my, my, my.  Over the past month,
Ukraine has recaptured more territory than
Russia has taken.
Where is this?
Come on, look.
Direction can you tell the direction
to Okay.  Orekhovskoye direction.
Low-tactical direction.  Yes.   Did
you fight?   Yes.
Look.  Yes.  Yours these.  In short, it's a race.
I'm telling you last month.  I don't look at
the dynamics of that year.  I'm looking at last
month.
And they just, in short, took two
steps.  These flag-stickers.
Flag-stickers.  Come on, take a look.
Provide deep pstate statistics for the past month.   Let's do it
in a year.
Well, let's do it in a year.  Okay, go ahead and talk.
Tell me, I'm interested in
how many classes you don't like over the course of a year,
let's say over six months.
Come on, come on, within a year.  In six months.  Yes.
Give me some data already, at least
tell me some.
Well, come on.  Well, no.  Wait.  If you
don't have data, why?
Come on, tell me the details.  You mean
in six months.  Go ahead and say them.
I 100% believe that it is like Ukraine.
Name this data.  Name the data.
Balance number.
And from January 2026. Yes, yes, yes.  Name
today's date.
Yes, give me the number.  How much did you win?
You won back zero.
How much did you win?
We didn't win it back, we captured it.
Captured.  How many?  How many?
A lot.
Well, tell me the number.  Let's see now.
Well, I'm just, well, listen, I'm just not as much of a
nerd as
No, well, wait.  Well, you operate with
some of us or the rear.
No, wait a minute.  Okay
, I get it.  You have no data.   Well, here it
begins.  You are ours by the meter.
Well, if there is, tell me this information.
Ah, well, okay.  I see, in short,
I'll be in a direct dialogue with you, 15,000 square meters,
150.
Well, say no, look, let's do it, you
said, let's open deepstate.  Okay, open it.   In
short, we paid 153,000.
Well, open it.  You said we'll open
deepstate now.  You've kind of disappeared.
How much should I arrange this for you?
153,167
sq.
Super.  And we are 253.157
square meters.  All.
Yes, you see, yes, like that,
you can say anything you want without any grounds, without any grounds.
So, now look, now tell me
how many oil refineries
Ukraine hit last year, the year before,
or in the last six months, let's take that.
Yes, I can say for all the time.
Let's.
30%.
30%.  Super.
How much do you think
?  Let's say
how much?  Ask your question.
Well, 30%.  And how many does Russia generate?
And logistics, for example, according to AZE and
your logistics.
How many of our gas stations are there?  Look, here in
Ukraine,
after the gas station, there are 5,000.
Look, 5,000 gas stations,
right?  In Ukraine.
How many gas stations are there in Ukraine?
And you know Wait, no, wait.  5,000
throughout Ukraine.  Do you know how many
oil refineries there were, in short?
One, I think.  Yes, yes, yes.  And you
also entered the data
correctly.  So, look,
Europe supplies us with fuel, we don’t care whether we have
oil refineries or not.  Look, in
my city there is gasoline and no
lines, but for some reason in your cities there is
no gasoline.  And you don’t have queues
because there is no gasoline.  Where to leave?
How come there isn't one?  Look, I went in,
bought some gas and that's it.  What do you have in
occupied Crimea?  Tell me, what's wrong with the
light?
And it stabilized automatically.
Destabilized.  Piz.   Yes.
No,
we bet.  Come on, show me that you're
stabilizing.  Show me.
I bet 5,000 hryvnia.
Come on,
come on,
come on.  Show, show the post.
How can I show you?
Well, read it.
You can come in and see it now.
Everything is fine.
Well, I do
n’t know, I think it was the day before yesterday.  The day before yesterday I
sort of took a bite
.
What is the bereavement
on this topic?   I'm
watching Aksyonov now.  He doesn't have it
.  Yes.  What?  stabilized.  Here
his Telegram came in.
And
show me, show me where it has stabilized.   Yes.
Show me where it isn't.   Right
there.  Unfortunately,
another enemy attack on northern
Crimea killed two people and
damaged energy infrastructure.
Today there will be power outages again according to the
unchanged schedule.
Show me where.  Show me where he said it.  So I
went to his Telegram channel Aksyonov Z82.
141,000
subscribers.  Come on, come in and show me
where he said he stabilized it.
I won't.
Understood?
Well, because, well, you still won’t
believe it, you understand?  You still won't read it anyway,
you won't read it.  I'll believe you,
read it.
Which one will you believe?  What kind of
protist are you?  Of course not.  You're more than just
laughing at this, like,
no, you know?  What's the joke?  Like, you're
laughing at the fact that, like, well, there's
nothing like that there.  You understand
that a bicycle would be ten times worse
.
Of course it will.  Yes, sure.  I'm
sitting without light now, yes.  I'm sitting without gas.
Of course, worse.  What will you do for us?
What will you do to us?
No, wait, wait, like it's going to be much, much
worse.  What to do?
Will.  Look, you've
been telling me since 22 that it will get worse, it will get
worse, it will get worse.  Yes, but Ukraine, well,
look, Ukraine, on the contrary,
has increased its militarization over the past 4 years.   Yes.
The West supplies her with money, the West
supplies her with fuel, the West supplies
missiles and drones, and Ukraine has been simply destroying everything for 4 years
without any problems.
You know, like cracking sunflower seeds,
oil refineries in Russia,
some marketplaces with someone.  True,
yes,
true, yes.  Look, there are only
two sides to every coin, you must admit.
Yes, it’s as you say, of course, on the
one hand everything is great, but
look at the other side of the coin.  What
from Ukraine?  Yes.  What?  What's there?  Ukra,
right?  Yes.  Look, in short,
all the people fled from Ukraine.
And all the residential, all this housing stock,
in short, is hidden.  Men's fund for the home.
Hiding.  Yes.  Why?  Question.  Look,
if all the people fled, and the men
are hiding, why haven’t you been able to
capture Kyiv yet?
Wait, listen, I'll tell you about Kyiv
now.
Okay, look.  No, that's right.  Look, if
we have no people left, what's the problem with
you getting to Kyiv with your own people?  So I'll
tell you.  You let me speak.
Tell.  I'm wondering where
you're just interrupting me.
So, we don’t have people.  How
can you not tell us
who you are fighting for?
Wait, let me say something.
I give, I permit.  I give permission again.
Thank you.  Thank you.  USA.  Yes, sure.  Yes.
Well,
I give my brother a Ukrainian, like freedom, like he
allows me to do at least something.  Do
you have some kind of will to
allow something?  It's that you can't do anything in life
.  At least here you can
influence something.  This is a brother.  Well, look.
And in terms of the fact that there are,
of course, few Ukrainians left, that’s understandable
, you yourself understand this,
right?  Yes.  So there are no more of us left,
no men,
of course.  Yes, but because the
catastrophic situation
is not just in a hole, but simply
if you dig even more out of the hole, in short, yes,
everything is rock bottom.
Then economic, wait,
economic, right?
No, well I agree,
right?  Then look, economic
catastrophe.  How
economically independent is Ukraine now, for example, from other countries?
Yes, everything depends, it depends.  Yes.  The question is,
look, why are you all Ukraine
economically, demographically, why
can’t you capture that Kyiv?   There is
no goal to capture [laughter] him.
What is your goal to receive information from your
oil refineries and
Viber?  This is the task.
Well, listen, what do you think, like, it would be
good if Russia
really captured Ukraine in 2-3 days?   If
this hadn’t happened, yes,
of course, of course, it wouldn’t have happened, yes, there wouldn’t have been any
destruction either in Ukraine or in Russia.
I, listen, I don’t understand, do you know why?
Putin feels sorry for us, Ukrainians, but he doesn’t
feel sorry for you, Russians.
How many Russian soldiers die and feel sorry for
it?
Oh, wait, wait.  Putin could have already
hit the banking hazelnut trees and that would be it.  And
end the war.
What's the point?  What's the point?   I would have
ended the war.  Who is the decider?  About
banks.  Yes, according to banks.  They are not the ones making
the decision.
And who?
Well, the British, the Americans.
Everything was then hazelnut all over Britain and
America.  Why not
?  So, it turns out we need to fight on how
many fronts?
Yeah.  So wait, do I understand correctly
that you are now fighting with the West,
and not with Ukraine?
Yes, this must be done by your hands, of course.
Everything is great.  Yes, super, it
turns out correctly.  This is
absolutely true.  We are a puppet of the
West.  Yes, sure.  No, that's not true.
I'm telling you that's how it is.  I confirm.   I can
see in your eyes that the cart No, this is
not sarcasm.  You are not fighting with I agree
that you are not fighting with Ukraine, you are fighting with the
West.  You defeated Ukraine in 2-3 days.
This is a fact.  You are nothing without the West.  The question is
now, right?  If you fight with the West,
the West takes away your oil
refineries, your military, your people, but in the West
people don’t die, oil refineries don’t explode
, warehouses don’t burn
, which means the West is tearing Russia apart
.
They are not tearing Russia apart, they are
tearing our two countries apart.  Yes,
that's right, that's right.  Absolutely
correct.  You see, I agree.  Here
we agree with you.  That is, look,
the West is at war with Russia, as a result
Russia and Ukraine suffer, but the West does not
suffer.  Is it true?
In this regard, they didn’t expect that
it would drag on for so long, because
they thought that Russia would be a little bit like, “
Yeah, well, in fact,
yeah, in fact.”  Look, I agree with you
.
Paketov, I agree with you.  Russia
is at war with the West, and Russia and
Ukraine are the ones suffering.  Is it true?   Yes.   Yes.
It turns out that the West is winning this war with
Russia.
Well, they didn't think it would
drag on like this, so they're already losing.
No, wait.  Well, look, the West is undermining
Russia’s economy,
Russia’s military potential, but in the West everything is calm.  In
the West, people don't sit under missiles.
Not anymore.  No.
Where, where in the West are some
missiles exploding?   It's
not about explosions there, you understand?  They
will get to the point where, of course, there will be
explosions there.  They just thought that it would all
happen much faster.
But in economic terms, they were
thinking that they would win in this regard
, but they didn’t think that it would
drag on for so long.  Yes.
Not for n years,
not for five.  They wanted it faster then.
Well, here's the question.  Wait.  Listen, you're talking,
go ahead and talk.
Yes, you say 45 minutes.  I give you
permission to remain silent.  Yes.
Speak.  Come on, talk.  I'm listening to you.   Yes.  Yes.
I give you permission to remain silent.
This is me showing it
.  Look, the West simply didn’t
expect that this conflict would
drag on for so long.
I agree,
because it was supposed to be resolved quickly in this conflict
,
that Russia would quickly weaken under the
amount of sanctions, under the
amount of pressure from the
West, the European Union, America, Britain,
and maybe, oh my God,
China would get involved, but
China, of course, didn't get involved.
Agree.
Well, that didn't work out.  and they cut off all
economic supplies,
non-economic supplies, for example, of
some energy resources, supplies of
some kind of strangulation, and all the
chains were broken, everything had to be
abruptly restructured, and all 20 of these
one patent sanctions, which, well, had
no effect, for example,
but not as catastrophically as, for
example, they had in mind, because
if the catastrophes had
happened then, wait, then there would not have been the twenty-
first package of sanctions, if
then
this package, perhaps, would have ended,
like, a third.
I completely agree.
But this did not happen.  And what they're
trying to do in a panic, you know?  Do
you agree to run away in panic?   You
can't run back in panic.  You won't back down and say
that nothing worked out for us
.  Guys, come on, back up
.
Agreed.  I absolutely agree.   Of
course, we
created all this in Ukraine.
They created it, yes,
we did.  We didn't succeed.  It didn't work
.  Agree.
We seemed to have somehow managed to pit all of this against each other.  This is what
they ruled.  They were pressuring.   Are
you kidding me?
No.
You will repeat after me after each phrase
.
I agree.  I show that I
agree.  Well, calm down.  No, well you don't have to
say that.
Why are you nervous?
Well, because it's kind of annoying.
I agree with this.  Well, we are like-minded
people.  We are of the same mind.  What are
we arguing about?  How are we like-minded
?  The West didn't count on it.  I
agree with all of this.  But look at the question.
Look how many Russian soldiers
died and how many Western soldiers
died.   What do
Western soldiers have to do with this?
Here.  How many civilians died in Belgorod
and other cities, while in the West they are
not dying?
It's not about how many people died,
you know?  The goal is different.
Another goal.
Which?  The goal is simply to economically drive
our two countries, our
two countries, back to the Stone Age, so that we
represent nothing economically.  If there was, if look,
if Ukraine was the
very first economy after ninety-one,
yes, the world economy
in Europe, Europe,
that's it.  And Russia, of course, weakened
after the collapse of the Soviet Union, but it...
Yes, but it also had to be put under pressure,
because there are a ton of resources and opportunities,
so what is the ideal way to put pressure on you and me
?  To take
and stir up this
Russophobic attitude of yours for 30 years,
right?  Russophobic.  We have politics,
I agree, in full swing here.
And that one, and that one is not so, and that one is not so.  Oh, yes,
for us, well, of
course, yes, the fact that you seem to
live so poorly is because Russia is to
blame, they
developed a Russophobic policy.  Russia
has always been our friend.  We were told that it was an
enemy.  What's wrong?  Look, after
ninety-first year you had full
metallurgy, full processing,
full
mechanical engineering
.  There were shipbuilding mechanical engineering
.  Nikolay is a
full-cycle metallurgy company,
from mining to processing.
Well, you agree,
right?  And where is this West?  What is he
right?  So look, not with us, but
with us and you.
I stuck it in you.  I stuck it in you.
Right.  Look, the West and Yes, the West
destroyed.  West.  Look, your Yeltsin and
Gorbachev, yes, sold the Soviet Union to the West
.  Well, agree.
Yes, yes, I agree.  Your Yeltsin and
Gorbachev,
they sold out to the West.  Gorbachev withdrew,
destroyed the Berlin Wall, withdrew troops
from Eastern Europe.  NATO immediately entered there
.  He also gave 15 of our Slavic
Soviet republics to NATO.  Yes.  And that's
all.  Then Putin started to
change something, yes.  But it was already too late.   Yes.  Yes.
Well, you, of course, are also like, you
know, you shouldn’t,
in short, you know, cut out your
Kuchma, for example, from this equation.  It's true.
And he is a pawn.  What?  If you look, if you
know, he is the same pawn as
Gorbachev, you understand?  This is [ __ ] [ __ ].
Wait, if someone
was in control of the power unit.  Gorbachev, if Gorbachev had given
the command, yes, and that’s it,
Yeltsin and Kuchma would never have gathered in Belorezhskaya Pushcha
.   Do you agree
?  In this regard, I agree with you
.  Yes, sure.  If he had given
the order to the security forces, like, let's go look
, in 1968 they actually
came to Prague by helicopter,
picked up the dubchik and brought him to Moscow, like
Madura is now, you know, and that's it
.
Generally speaking, yes.  That's all, Gorbachev.  Why?
Because he was an agent of the West.  He had already
surrendered the Soviet Union.  Soviet Union.
The troops were stationed from East Germany, from
Berlin to Sakhalin, you understand?  And no one
dared to say anything to the Soviet Union
.  And now you and I don’t
understand, well,
yes, I just completely agree with you
.  Yes.  If he had,
if he had, of course,
bigger brains, that is what he had,
of course, it was necessary to introduce this.  And
now,
yes, I don’t, that’s clear.
Now we are all Slavs, Ukrainians,
Russians, Belarusians, this was one people
since the time of Rurik.  Well, agree,
right?  He wasn't, he is.  It just
is.  We are one people.  Well, do you agree that
we are one people?   Yes.   That's it
.  Look.  And what happens?  Now,
instead of bombing the
Anglo-Saxon decision-making centers of
Brussels, London, Berlin and Washington,
yes, they are bombing Bakhmut, Konstantinovka, and
Russian cities in Donbass.  That's where the
Russians lived.  So, you also
understand, between the fact that, like, like
, you guys, we are not fighting against
this.  And how can we say, well, like
, guys,
look, so many of you have come from Western Ukraine since
1991, yes, since
1991 the Americans have been putting us in
power.  We don't have elections
.
We don't have elections.  The Americans put us in
power, they tell us who they elected and that's it
.
Well, you see, you understand. What are
we going to do?  What shall we do?  You know,
it's like in a restaurant, whoever pays the bill gets it
. We haven't paid them since 1991.  Yes, that's
true.  And look, the question is
why, yes, why Putin is
destroying Russian cities, I don’t understand.
Bakhmut is a Russian city, 70,000 Russians
lived there, you understand?  There is no such thing,
you know it straight away,
he... Yes, he doesn't want to destroy, but in
fact, don't
wait.  No, your
statement is somewhat strange, as if he
wants to destroy Bakhmuti.  No, he didn’t
want to, but in fact he destroyed it.
Yes, because there were troops there.
And I'll explain to us something sweet, look
how it should be done, Marshal, how
Marshal Zhukov would have done it.  Girth in pincers, yes, that's all.
And why, in short, war, the war of the 20th century
and the war of the 21st century.  Do you remember, for example,
when, for example, Marshal
Rakosovsky, when he said, like,
oh my God, well, these
eskatrons, they are absolutely no longer needed,
because machine guns and tanks have already appeared
.   Do
you remember?
I remember.
By the
way, Rakosovsky was Polish.   What
I mean is that every war brings its own
new
innovations, well, how should I
say it, like some
innovations, you know, drones, you know, like
now, where are the tank troops
now, who needs them there?
Well, wait, just watch, I'm like Well, I'm
actually a Russian person, yes, I don't consider
myself Ukrainian, I'm Russian.  My father is
from Ryazan, yes, my mother is from Orenburg, I am
Russian.  They studied here in Kharkov during the
Soviet Union.  I was born in
1981 in Kharkov, yes, in the Russian
city of Kharkov.  I've always
spoken Russian, you understand?  I communicate with you
as a Russian communicates with a Russian.  And I ca
n’t understand, maybe you can explain it to me in Russian
.  Look, the
West is fighting against our Russian
people, the three united Russias.
Yes, it turns out that Putin, instead of, like
Stalin, leading troops to
Berlin
and giving those Anglo-Saxons a beating, he
takes some cities in Donbass where
Russian people live and speak
Russian, you understand?
Well, yeah, wait.  No, well listen, wait.
Well, you live as if in some kind of utopia.
You know, it's not like,
"Oh my God, let's just go and blast the
entire European Union and some
specific West," right?  It's like it's
like the hegemon of evil.  But not with this America, that's
not how it works in big politics.
Understand?  In big politics there are no
eternal friends and eternal enemies.  There are
eternal interests.
Got it.
Yesterday's enemies will become your
friends today.  Today's friends
will become your enemies tomorrow.  This, by the way, was proven by
excellent policy, for example, when a
terrorist, for
whose head a price of
10 billion dollars was offered, became the ruler of Syria.
Horror.   Yes.
And when Bashar al-Assad was overthrown, he
came to power, and Donald Fredovich Trump shakes hands with him
.
And there was a 10 billion dollar bounty on his head,
you know?
Agree.  Yes.  This is Syrian.   Yes.  Yes.  Yes.
But there is no
such thing in big politics.  I agree with you too, but you don't
understand, if you're a ruler and you
come to a class and say,
"Lord, we have these eternal
friends, these guys, these guys, give
them nuclear missiles. It doesn't work that way. It does
n't work. I agree."
I want this.  This is what ordinary
people want.  This is what ordinary people want.
Lord, let's put an end to this
damned West.  Well, it doesn't work that way.
I want this.
Well, that's not possible.  No, you understand, it’s
impossible.  Agree.
It is forbidden.  Well, no, it’s possible, but it doesn’t
work.   It
doesn't work.  Yes, I agree, we don’t
argue about that.
I gave you an example with the ruler of Syria,
you see, they offered 10 billion dollars for his head
.
Yes,
the same Americans, you know?  They
called him an ISIS member.  Yes, I agree.  He,
no, he, you know, how it is,
like in the Wild West it’s like, you know, it
hung.  This was wanted.  W wanted the
10 billion photo ad,
right?  10 billion. Went to class after
bash rasada.  That's it, that's it, in short, the
European leaders have arrived, you understand?
European leaders came to see him.  This is all about what a
wonderful person he is.  Although this
wonderful man committed genocide.   There is
genocide there, right?
Christians in several provinces,
yes, there was horror there, in short, there was
such a massacre.
Yes, I agree.  Listen, here's the question.
Well, uh, Putin came to protect Russian
people in Ukraine, right?  Yeah, Putin's
just, damn, you know, he's saying,
"No, Putin's just a victim of
circumstances here. Yeah, yeah, I agree. There was
no other way to act,
you know?
You do it, you know? It's like in
chess, for example, zugzwa.
Zukzwa, zug, zang.
Zung. Well, I'm saying zugzwa.
Zug, not zung, but zug, zwang.
I get it. Well, you get what I'm talking about.
Like, whatever move you make, it's always going to
lead to something bad
. Putin was forced. Putin was forced. There's no
point in waiting any longer. If he'd
waited, Ukraine would have attacked first.
Well, it's not that they would have attacked first, it would have just been, like,
in Donbas,
for example, some kind of bloody mess. A
bloody mess. But right now,
there's no bloody mess in Donbas, right?
It's bad enough anyway. And so,  It's
bad as it is.
Well, so and so, yes, yes, I agree. Well, they'll
just get what all this would
lead to, because it's
unclear, yes. But now it's clear what it
led to, yes. Look, Bakhmut is destroyed,
Konstantinovka is destroyed.
I agree with you, like, I would also
like for this to end in, like, three days
. Well, like, well, how does this
happen, like, it's just simply
incomprehensible. I don't understand.
Well, how does it turn out that Putin, yes,
I had a friend, Sanya Prokhorov, he's from
Bakhmut, yes, he's also Russian. I
tell him: "Listen, get out, there's going to be an
OBO." He says: "No, I'm Russian,
yes, Putin will come to save me." I
say: "But he doesn't even know you." And,
anyway, he was standing there,
some missile flew, like, into his house, in
short, and that's it. Sanya Pro died, a Russian
man waiting for the Russian army. And what
happens? 70,000 residents of Bakhmut
Russian people. I don't understand, did Putin
make it better or worse for them.
Yes. Well, listen, you're just somehow, you
know, you're just taking these
global thoughts.
Global, yes, I agree. No, no,
specifically for some specific individual,
you know, there's no such type in global
politics, well, it doesn't work that way.
This, you know, I'm, of course, giving a crude
example, it might sound like, you
know, have you ever played
some kind of strategy computer
game, like civilization, for example, right?
Well, or maybe a regular
strategy game, yes, you have a goal.
I don't play games.
Well, I've never played any of them.
Well, like, well, there's still
some kind of global goal there, like
this or that country, well,
yes, either to capture it or somehow
hold on to it. You don't have a goal, like
you don't have one, but as for units, your units don't have a
last name
or  A name, nothing. Just a unit, a unit, an
infantryman, an assault trooper, there's a city,
there's just so many people in the city,
there's nothing. And so, and as the
leader of your country, you
shouldn't, like, think about how,
like, Vasya Ivanov
will die in this situation. Of course, it's a pity.
A pity, yes. But, you see, you do
n't think in terms of every person, you think in terms of the
size of your country. The
country,
yes. And how will your country in this situation have to
either lose something, or
something,
or gain something? Yes, here, of
course, for example, if there's a 10% loss,
for example, of the country, but the benefit, for example,
will be the same as if, for example, in
military terms, you
carry out some kind of intervention on
the territory of another country, but you, for
example, will subsequently win some kind of...
you have a preference in one way or another
. Preference, I agree. Yes, if there is a
preference, yes, but you won't have a
list of people in front of you,
like Petrov and Ivanov,  Sidrov and so
on. I understand, I feel sorry for everyone, I feel sorry,
of course. I feel sorry for them rolling in the street. You too,
of course, I do. Well, what can you do, I
agree. There's nothing you can do about it.
All this
, you see, is a global reorganization of
the world. A
global reorganization, yes.
I agree with you. Like, I feel sorry for everyone. I feel sorry for
everyone.
Well, what can you and I do?
Come on. You and I can only, like,
go yelling down the street, right? You
can yell at home. Here you can yell at me
. Can you change anything globally
?
No, I globally agree. You can't do anything
. Yes.
Well, you and I can only talk about it
and say how bad it is
or how good it is, for example, right? Like
this, or how that, what
consequences we will carry out this. But on a
global level, you and I can't
sing about this at all. You, of course, will say something
like: "Yeah, go out on the street, well, go out on the
street."
What are you  You'll do it? You can't do anything.
He'll say, like, he
screwed up, of course, no, I
agree.
Only you and I can, like,
discuss it,
diagnose it, you know, this
, how it infuriates me,
to analyze it from a legal point of view, this, like, this, this, this, this, he's like, this, this, this, this,
yes, I agree with
you on all this. Here's the question, listen, I just agree with you
on all this. I don't understand
one thing. As a Russian, yes, I
understand why our triune Russian
people, yes, like, Russians, Belarusians,
Ukrainians, yes, suffer from the West. Why
, well, let's put it this way. Did Putin
make things better or worse for the Russian residents of Bakhmut
?
Why are you so attached to this Bakhmut?
Well, because 70,000 Russian people
lived there. 70,000. So, these are military operations,
you know? That's
right, right? I just... Let's do it this way. As
a result of all these actions  For
the residents of Bakhmut, did it get better or worse?
Yes, you see, these are just military
operations. You understand,
agree? These are military operations, not
civil actions. Yes. So as
a result [laughter] of these battles,
because it was a strategic city,
you understand? So as a result, yes, I
understand that Putin, yes, was forced to
take Bakhmut, but as a result of
this capture of Bakhmut, he was forced to take.
Then I can, you know, ask you a question point-blank
. For example, when Zelensky came
to power and said that we will,
in short, we will abandon the Minsk
agreements and will develop a nuclear
bomb, he did it to the advantage of the Ukrainian
people.
To the disadvantage. Agreed. This is a disadvantage, right?
Agreed.
Well then. And there were no military operations yet,
right? Yes. Now, right? And now,
yes, I'm asking you about Bakhmut. So, after all,
for the residents of Bakhmut, well,
because 70,000 Russian people there
disappeared somewhere. So for these Russians  People, the fact
that Putin was forced to take Bakhmut, did he
make things better for the residents of Bakhmut or worse?
Listen, these are military operations. I disagree here
. These are military operations, not police operations, not
civilian operations, but military operations. So, as
a result of these military operations, whether
you want a yes or no answer, I will not tell you that it is
not I who want things better or worse. Are the residents of
Bakhmut now better or worse? Is that what
you want from me? Do you hear me?
Yes. I want a clear answer from you. Are the
residents of Bakhmut better or worse off? The answer that you will really like. I do not have any answer of yours. It's just that the residents of Bakhmut are better off or worse off?
You know that yourself, this answer. It's clear
that... Yes, of course, it's clear.
Naturally, yes, but wait, well, these are
military operations. I agree. Military
operations. Wait. Okay, then no,
wait,
wait, wait. Then these military
operations. Okay, if you say let's
go, but why don't you get down to it?  calculation?
Like, don't you want to say, like, isn't
Zelenskyy to blame for this, that he,
for example,
Zelenskyy is to blame, that's clear.
Zelenskyy is to blame, right? Wait,
no, wait. The residents of Bakhmut, don't
wait. The residents of Bakhmut should
thank Zelenskyy for, like,
arranging this for them.
Well, look,
for the fact that he refused low
agreements.
The residents, yes, the residents of Bakhmut are angry at both
Zelenskyy and Putin. Agreed. Yes, yes.
No, wait, wait. What does
Putin have to do with this? Oh, wasn't Zelenskyy 6
days before 20?
Zelenskyy agrees. Yes, 6 days
he said.
No, no, wait. I think
6 days before the invasion. Yes, he said,
yes, about dirt.
No, no, wait, wait. No, on
February 18th of '22 he started
bombing this.
Yes, he started bombing. Yes.
They shouldn't  tell him.
They must. I agree.
So, why are you
asking this question exactly?
Okay, that's right. No, look. So, Zelensky,
look, Zelensky is a puppet of the West.
Everything is clear here. Well, Putin is not. And why are
you putting him at the top of the list?
Look. No, I understand. Zelensky is
a puppet of the West, but Putin is a defender of the
Russian people, right?
So you, in short, are simply
blaming all this, ours, on this, on
this.
I just can't. Look again.
Zelensky is a puppet of the West. Everything is
clear here, I don't argue with that, I agree.
Question. But in my eyes, Putin has always
been a defender of the Russian people. And what would
you do, for example, in Putin's place in
this situation?
In Putin's place... I'm telling you, look, I would
n't destroy Russian people in Donbas,
right? I would, listen, launch, look,
launch a hazelnut without a warhead,
warn Western partners,
You say: "By the way, it hasn't been there yet." Well
, it's here now, right?
You say: "So, dear Western
partners, at 14:88 we will
launch a hazelnut missile without a warhead at you to
show our serious intentions.  And
if after this you supply
the Nazi, Kyiv regime with all these
drones, guns, yes, we will give you a
good bang." And I'm telling you,
listen, if
this hazel tree fell in some field, even in Germany, and everyone
would understand everything,
right? That's what you want, you know? That's what
many people want, you know,
to somehow
end the conflict quickly. But, you see, people,
I think that some General Staff,
somewhere in the government,
analysts, they calculate the risks 100%.
What do you think, for example, if
someone did this, well, like either
Russia there, or something, yes, well, let's say
Russia, yes, we're sorting out Russia. What do you
think is the percentage,
what percentage of the probability that all
NATO countries would get involved and immediately start attacking
Russia? That's a big percentage. A big, big one
.
That's why I do, well
, that's why analysts, I think, like
calculate such-and-such a probability  That,
of course, but Dan doesn't want it, I think
everyone wants their hands just like that,
red fingers there, rubbing that
button.
That's what they want.
Well, what's the percentage that we'll
turn the whole planet into dust, you know?
Just into dust.
These people who make
decisions, who were created in Ukraine, and what
they did, it's Britain, there's
America, there's I don't know who supplies
this, the Germans, the French, the Poles. Yes,
of course, it would be possible to press three
buttons, yes, fly them off the face of the earth, but
what's the percentage probability that for the
next 15,000 years we'll
just be able to go out without a
smear on our faces?
Well, there's no such percentage. And it's just
not possible to do it. That's why we have to
dodge like this, you know, I do
n't like that phrase, I don't like that
phrase, like, you know,
and somehow dodge between
these scum and say something like, well,
like, we're cooperating with you today
, but not tomorrow  We cooperate.
Well, trying, you know, it's like
coming in at Formula 1, trying to be first among a
gigantic mass of cars that are
just rushing forward somewhere, without
bumping into anyone, so as not to provoke a
gigantic accident, in that sense.
Well, yes.
So it turns out, listen, it turns out that the
West has made Russia hostage of this
situation. Yeah, yeah.
Damn, the West is a very cunning chess player
. Yeah. So, in that sense, they're
very well-trained. It's not for nothing that they've
been busy for
100 years pumping up this
media of theirs. They had wonderful,
they had wonderful teachers. It wasn't for
nothing that they carried out operations after
World War II and took everyone out,
yes, even the ideologists and scientists
from the
Third Reich.
I agree.
Regarding brainwashing. The Third Reich
- that was number one at the time.
I agree.
They took note of it. And
look how well it works.
Some kind of fart, they  They're
handing it out, guys. That's true, that's it, it's
just a gigantic gap in the media. Plus
this media, which is paid for in
many countries. That's the most terrible and the
most horrific thing, that billions of dollars are being paid for in many countries, in
many states
. It's
just these TV companies, these
various intermedia, which...
Well, yes, their intermedia agrees there.
And what, what attracts people the most
? It's, for example, their minds, so
to speak, their
imagination. This is what they see and
hear. And what do they hear and see for the
most part? It's the media
that is happening in the country. Listen, well,
yes, look, there's nothing wrong with that. Understandable.
The West is a quintessence, it's the global
axis of evil. Yes, Ukraine is its. But still, once again
, yes, it turns out that the West forced
Putin to make sure that
Russian people die on both sides of the border. Both
Russian people in Ukraine and Russian people in
Russia. So
no, no, that's not exactly true.  forced, but
simply led to this. Led, yes,
led. It turns out that listen, well, it
seems to me, well, Putin, well, he is such a
great geostrategist. Couldn't he really
come up with anything other than to turn this
situation into something where Russians
kill Russians?
Listen, in this regard, they also
miscalculated a little, because they
thought that, like, yes, when they
led Russia to this conflict, they thought,
like, Russia, of course, would explode a little,
then we would put a little pressure, and
Russia would
quickly
crumble, and we, in short,
quickly, quickly get Russia going.
They misread a little in the sense
that we were preparing for this. So you're
wrong to say that Putin isn't such a
great geostrategist. He's not a stupid
man. And we have been preparing for this
conflict, yes, since 2014,
because we completely changed
our economic structure, specifically the
banking one,  Yes, when everyone immediately
thought that if we disconnect
our Russia from Swift, the entire
economic
component of our state will collapse.
But it won't collapse. I
disagree.
Yes, yes, yes. Because we created a
structure independent
from the global, uh, economic system,
yes, from Swift. There you go. Then, over the course of these
several years, we developed new
ballistic systems, the kind that...
Yes, yes. Yes, something like that. Borevestnik,
Kinzhal. The same thing. Dagger. Well
, that's later. Here's the very first dagger.
Well, yes, I already agree,
yes. Hypersonic missiles.
There you go. And so, of
course, the West thought a little that
Russia's economic component would
collapse a little because it thought it would
collapse. I agree with that, they didn't expect it.
And in terms of the fact that even
if energy flows are cut off, yes, that
happened later, like we're undermining
some...  Oil, gas. I agree,
they undermined it, right?
Yes. No, they undermined it, yes. But it
didn't change anything, because we
had perestroika.
Economic perestroika,
yes, and all these flows, the flows of
exports, exports, imports, they are
so flexible here that
they are flexible, by the way, yes, not like in
the West.
Well, no, in the West they don't have it either, it depends on which
West. It depends on which West.
If you take America, they are even more flexible there
.
And there, listen, have you seen
America's national debt?
Oh, yeah, who cares. Listen,
there they simply, in short, the national debt in general, they
already owe the whole world.
No, well, the national debt there, in fact, doesn't have
any effect on the
economic component of that very
West, because, you know, it's like I
said before, like the
sun never sets on Britain.
Now the sun doesn't set on the United States  It
works because the United States
is the biggest colonizer of the entire
world.
Yes, their national debt is horrendous. Yes, it's a
national debt, my God. And they'll write it off
later, when they
agree to write it off,
under the pretext that you'll
tell us you owe it.
Well, yes,
and not we you. That is, you see, that's
it. Listen, the result of
all this
activity is that, yes, Russian people are dying in
Russia and Russian people in Ukraine. Do
you agree?
Yes.
I agree. Question. If Russian
people are dying in Russia and Russian people in Ukraine,
and in the West it's not dying, but the
Russian people who are dying, is that playing into the hands of the West or
Russia?
Well, the West, of course.
Of course, the West. Am I right in understanding
that Putin, by introducing this special military
operation, is playing into the hands of the West?
No. No.
So what are you [laughter]? It's beneficial
to the West.
So, you understand that, but if we
stop, then what happens?  Like,
the West will win, right? What will they ask us
to do? Okay, we're like,
Vladimir Vladimirovich comes out today and
says, "That's it, we're stopping."
And the West comes out and says, "Yes, of course, that's it,
you're stopping, withdrawing your
troops." Do you understand? There's no
compromise anymore, it's impossible to come to this.
They'll say, "No,
don't stop, Ukraine." They say, it's
right, like it was, for example,
there at the beginning of 2022. And
so look, wait,
wait, wait. No, wait, wait.
Like, we wanted to stop. You
remember, at the beginning of 2022
we wanted, yes, the Istanbul Agreements.
Agreed.
No, this is not this, it was April.
April in Istanbul. April was, yes. The
Istanbul Agreements, yes.
You were already leaving Kyiv by August, yes,
I agree.
Like, that's it, let's go. This is peace, friendship,
chewing gum. In short, we've arrived, guys. Ah, the
hairy shaggy one from  Britain said:
"Yes, this is corn." Yeah,
yeah, yeah. No, guys,
you haven't fought enough. You haven't
lost enough. Let's give everything. Let's
give everything. Let's just stop the bear
as long as possible, as much
and as hard and as vigorously as possible.
And notice, no matter how many
situations there are, they won't
talk, they'll say: "Yes, we'll
always agree on this now
, that we'll agree on everything now
."
Now we are organizing a club, we
are negotiating." Tomorrow we will create a club, we are
not negotiating. Then I
agree.
This will go on indefinitely, until we,
at most, two countries, Ukraine and
Russia, economically destroy
each other's main business.
Look, it turns out that the West is now
simply watching Russia and Ukraine
destroy each other, right?
And is this economically beneficial for everyone?
Yes. That's the question.
Look, look, the most important thing is
clear, right? So, look, so why?
I just can't understand. I agree with you on
everything, right? I can't understand one thing.
So why does Putin continue to destroy
Russians?
Well, wait. Well, I'm telling you again,
if we stop, if we
stop, [snorts] it will be
much worse.
How much worse? You are a nuclear power.
Who could jump on a nuclear power? I
mean, who? Here they are,
jumping. It's all just whoever is feeling lazy.
Who? How do you imagine that someone
could attack  A nuclear power?
Okay. How do you imagine
, for example, stopping
Vladimir Vladimirovich's country? Like, "
Wait, look, I agree with you, right?"
Like, it's being restored, Vladimir
Vladimirovich comes out, and that's it,
Donbas is ours, according to Ukraine? They'll say,
"No, no, that's not it
, look, what's the point?"  The
point is that no matter what conditions, in short,
Russia puts forward,
Ukraine will 100% not fall for these conditions,
because the West will not fall for this.  Because
Why?  Look, there are simple conditions on
which you can stop.  Look, Russia is an
example, a simple,
simple example.  Look, if Russia
withdraws its troops from Crimea, Donetsk,
Lugansk, Bryansk Oblast, Kursk,
Belgorod, Rostov, Voronezh, and
Krasnodar Krai, these territories
go to Ukraine, and that's it, the
war stops.  And there is
no more bloodshed.
And that's how it is, that's how I did it.
That's how it is.
Okay, look.  So, Russians will not
kill Russians.
Do it like this.  So.
So, Russians will stop killing Russians.
Well, do it like this.
Wait, are the lives of Russians
or the territories more important to you?   What do
you want, territories?  Why do you need
so many territories?
Come on, look, come on, come on then, let's
turn this coin over to the
other side.  Agree?
In short, do you agree to a world without Crimea,
Donetsk, Lugansk, the Zaporizhzhia and
Kherson regions?
No.
You see, this is
dogo. Look here.  Okay, look again.
Because we, Ukraine, need
territories.  Do you, Russians, need
territories or people’s lives?
We need peace, to be rewarded.  That's it, peace.
If you need peace, we offer you
peace.  Look, we don't need peace.  Ukraine
needs territories, and you need peace.  Okay,
bingo.  Common denominator.  You give us
Belgorod, Kursk, Rostov,
Krasnodar regions.  And there will be peace.
You get the world, we get
the territories.
This is how I'll do it.  No, come on
, wait one more time.  Look, you wanted
peace, you will get peace.
Well, of course, you also rolled it out destructively.   Like,
you have
n't been keeping an eye on your territories since 1991, and
now you want five more territories,
which are my territories?
My territories are only expanding.
No, no, I mean the right,
I am not a citizen of Israel at all.
No, I mean Well, I mean
Ukraine, like,
look at that.  Hello, wait, I'm not from
Ukraine.
What difference does it make to me,
I'm an Israeli citizen.  I live in Israel.
Well, that's understandable.
This is another hour and a half of conversation.
Wait, on the contrary, our territory
is expanding
on No, come on, listen, come on, on to the
second series.  This is No,
wait.  So what's wrong?
What's wrong?
No, I have a separate topic for Israel
.  No,
what separate one?  So look, our
people are our people, whether in Ukraine,
Russia, America, everyone.  No, no.  Well,
no, well
, and you, you’re like, Russians are killing
Russians, right?
Listen, well, damn, you see, you too,
who just, you know,
pulled it on your finger, in short, the West,
put you in this way, Israel is twisting you like this
, you see?
Here.  And you feel like you
rule the world, but in reality, you’re just
spinning around like this, you
know?
Agree.
This is what you, Israel, are like,
and you think that you rule this
world.  In fact, this is how,
you know, they are promoting you and doing what
those very elites and
oligarchs and billionaires want, in order to
create some kind of conflict somewhere
or to destabilize some kind of
situation.
Agree.  By the way, do you agree that there are a lot of
oligarchs in Russia and
Jews in the government?
Listen, it seems to me that you are everywhere and all
over the place.
Well, do you agree?
Well, not directly, like, well, look.  Well,
I agree, less than 10%, well, about
10% there are Jews in the oligarch’s Russia and that’s it.
Agree?  No, less, less than 10%.
That is, the Jews in Russia there, in short, are
some kind of process of oligarchs there, up to
10%.
Well no, well 10 you went too far.  No,
well, of course there are
five.  Give me five each.  Twentieth.  Yeah,
well, what five?  I say
less than 1%, but they exist.
Understood.  Question.
And who can you name
at least one?  Look, you
have oligarchs in Russia.  Azerbaijanis,
Tatars, Chechens, in short, Jews.
Can you name at least one Russian
oligarch?
Listen, I’ll just, if I need to look,
I’ll, of course, prepare for this
conversation later, like, we need to look at the lists, yes, we
need to look at them.  I don't know, look at this.
Rotenberg, yes, this is our Yurei.  Alisher
Usmanov, Uzbek, yeah, that's who it is,
anyway
, Friedman Miller.
Friedman Miller, yes.  Our people, yes.
Abramovich is ours and so on.  Yes,
our boys, our boys.
Derepaska is Ukrainian, yes, who else is there,
in short, this one,
listen, just wait.  Well,
the Kovalchuks are Ukrainians, the Rotenbergs and
Rotenbergs are our Jews.  All.  And who is
Russian?
Yes, we need to take a look.  We need to take a look.
Well, at least they do that.  Why Russians?
Why can't Russians even become oligarchs in their own country
?
Damn, well, the Russians, you see, they’re just sort of
doing some
science there.
Can you name me a modern Russian scientist?
Well, you hand over such things that
I really need exactly this.
Fine.  Name any Russian scientist of the
20th century.
You're making fun of
Well, you said, look, I
named so many Jewish oligarchs, and you said the
Russians are engaged in science.  Well, who's
watching?  Kapitsa was a Jew.  100% there is.
Landau was Jewish.  Yes.  Who did
you find?  Whom?  Ask.  I'm not really like, that's how
you said science.  Well, name these
Russian scientists.
Well, look, we bet they exist.
Well, name some Russian scientists from the 20th century.
I'm not a particularly smart person.  You're not getting to that,
but I agree with you on this point.  Not particularly smart.
Agree.
You Yes, yes, yes.  You're
coming to the wrong place.
Agree.  Here, listen, this is the
quintessence of our conversation.  I
completely agree with you here.
Well, yes, you're starting to be sarcastic again.
Of course I can come to you, I can come to you the same way
.  It's the same thing, it's a thesis, to
you from
No, well, you said that you're not very
smart, Czechs.  I completely agreed here.
Yes, I don’t deny it, you understand?  Well,
I don't deny it either.
And unlike you, like, yes,
I would also apply this thesis to myself.  Well,
you know, like you present yourself
as like hyper-intelligent, like, but nothing like that.
I am smart, hyper-smart.
Well, yes, you see,
everything [snorts] is clear.  Hyper,
well, you see, look.  And on this we
agreed.  Let's.  That's it,
the Russian is
gone.
[laughter]
Agree?  Write in the chat, will you?
Write in the comments or agree.
[laughter]
Like, subscribe, comment.  Subscribe to
our WhatsApp channel.  Here is the QR code.  There,
news similar to that
in the Telegram channel is posted for those who don’t have
Telegram or who don’t use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.